- Is this the last scene?
- Yes
This is the last one
You're going
to a wrap party?
Sure
And on set today…
Hyesung
Sorry, I'm late
Yoo-il
How did you know
I'm here?
Your manager told me
I heard it's the last day
of shooting
Are you not happy
I'm here?
I'm just a bit cold
Are you okay?
It's cold outside, right?
Why don't you wait
somewhere warm
during shooting?
No, I'm here
to watch the shooting
Hyesung
we're starting soon
Okay then…
Can you go get an iced
Americano for me?
You said you're cold
Hyesung
Hwi-rim
It was you
All those moments
passed through me
was all you
Cut!
Hyesung, what's wrong?
Let's focus
Yeah
Let's do it one last time
Okay, keep roll!
This one too
Okay, let's go!
Two, three! Action!
All those moments
passed through me
was all you